Guide to the Heinz Eulau Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2004-55
  - Elite Analysis and Democratic Theory: The Contribution of Harold D. Lasswell, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Ch. 15 The Hoover Elite Studies Revisited, undated (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Ch. 16 The Columbia Studies of Personal Influence, undated (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Ch. 17 On the Search for Political Party Identification, undated (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Ecological Correlations and the Behavior of Individuals, 1950 Jun. (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Cross-National Comparisons Using Aggregate Data: Some Substantive and Methodological Problems, undated (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Applications of an Expanded Survey Research Model to Comparative Institutional Studies, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Laboratory for Political Science, undated (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - American Political Science Review, A Critique of Nonmanipulative Research Design, undated (Box 28, Folder 45)
  - Case Analysis and Theory Construction, undated (Box 28, Folder 46)
  - A Theory of Political Ambition: Career Choices and the Role of Structural Incentives, 1972 Mar. (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Conflict in the Community: A Theory of the Effects of Community Size, undated (Box 28, Folder 48)
  - Theory and Politics, undated (Box 28, Folder 49)
  - Biological and Cultural Evolution, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 50)
  - Common Fate, Similarity, and Other Indices of the Status of Aggregates of Persons as Social Entities, undated (Box 28, Folder 51)
  - Assorted reviews, undated (Box 28, Folder 52)
  - Comparing Micro and Macro, Approaches to Institutional Analysis, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 53)
  - 20. Quality vs. Quanitity, undated (Box 28, Folder 54)
  - Academic Culture MSS (1/2), undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Academic Culture MSS (2/2), undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - The Congress as Research Arena: An Uneasy Partnership between History and Political Science, 1993 Nov. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Warran E. Miller and the Study of Comparative Politics: Mostly Some Personal Recollections and Reflections, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Bibliography: Heinz Eulau, 1941-1985, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Pathways to Democracy, Programs and Perspectives, 2002 Mar. 26 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Elite Analysis and Democratic Theory, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - The Hoover Elite Studies Revisited, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Classes and Interests in teh Early American Consciousness, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - What then is the American, this New Man? Some Preliminary Remarks on Citizenship and Community in the U.S.A., 1981 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Some Aspects of Analysis, Measurement and Sampling in The Transformation of Micro- and Macro-Level Unit Properties, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Photos mailed to William P. Shulhof, undated (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Judaica, 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Rabbi Adin Steinsaltz article, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Eash Northport Jewish Center papers, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Passover: Renewing an Ancient Conversation, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - JUDEN in der ehemaligen Tschechoslowakei, 36021 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Gray DAwn: The Jews of Eastern Europe in the Post-Communist Era, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Geschichte des Aufbau, 36358 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Hitler's Social Revolution Special Subject, EVerday life in the 1930s/ Truth and memory: memories of a Holocaust survivor of her school days, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Assorted articles on the Holocaust, Jewish people, Zionism, etc., undated (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Partial Transcript of Tape, G. Gunther, Growing Up in Nazi Germany, 32632 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Rue Eulau Paris, undated (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Various address printouts, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - The World Boko of Eulaus, undated (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Die Perle der Wetterau, undated (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - The American Journal of Economics and Sociology, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - I will Bear Witness: A Diary of the Nazi Years 1933-1941, 1998 Dec.28 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Family Tree Maker Magazine, undated (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Civilization magazine, 1998 Jun.-Jul. (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Genealogy articles, undated (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - The New Israel: Mosaic of Identities, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 32)